momvantage.net 2014-11-09

# Disclosure Policy & Privacy Policy

### Disclosure:

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact  jessie AT momvantage DOT net.

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

Affiliate links are used throughout this site.

**In regards to Giveaways:**

Please allow up to 6 weeks for delivery of prize. I will attempt to contact the sponsor on your behalf if you do not receive your prize after 6 weeks however I am NOT responsible for sponsors that don’t send prizes or things that are lost in the mail.

### Privacy Policy:

Your privacy is very important to us and we are committed to protecting it. We do ask for your email address when you leave a comment on MomVantage.net. This is used to verify comments, and is never sold or shared unless you are the winner of a giveaway. Only then will we use the information to contact you to inform you of your winning submission, and all appropriate information will be forwarded to that particular sponsor so they can send you your prize (ie. if it’s an e-gift certificate). If your mailing address is needed to claim your prize, we will only send this to the sponsor for prize shipment. No one else will have access to any of the personal information that you have provided.

This site contains ads from Google Ads and other third party vendors. These ads use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. You will also find links to third party websites on this site. We are not responsible for their privacy policies so please check with the individual site’s own privacy policy should have a concern.

We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact me at Jessie@MomVantage.net
